thereceptionist.com 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy - The Original Visitor Management System

## The Receptionist for iPad Privacy Policy

_Updated: August 2016_

This Privacy Policy explains the manner in which The Receptionist for iPad collects, uses, handles and discloses information about you that is collected in the course of your visit to our website, your access to and use of our products and services (“Service”) and your other interactions with us.

##### Personally Identifiable information

We do not collect any personally identifiable information about you when you visit our website unless you voluntarily disclose such information to us; such as when you register an account with us, fill out a form or elect to use certain features on our website. We do require basic contact information should you choose to order our Service, such as your and/or your company’s name, email address, mailing address and phone number. We also require payment information (such as a valid credit card number) for Service that is not free, but payment is handled by a third-party service provider and we do not process, store or otherwise take custody of or responsibility for this payment information. Ultimately, you have control over whether you visit our website anonymously, and you can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information, although doing so may restrict your access to certain features on our website as well as to our Service.

Our Service enables our customers to collect, store and manage data about themselves, their employees or their own customers and guests. For example, our customers may ask that visitors to their offices check in at a registration stand or desk using the Service by providing their name, address and other basic contact information, as well as their check-in and check-out times. These visitors may also be asked to take a picture and share additional information such as a date of birth or license plate number. The Service automatically creates a record of this information (e.g., a visitor log) that we collect and store for the limited purposes set forth below. Our customers are responsible for choosing what visitor data they wish to collect and for ensuring that their visitors consent to the collection of such data. For more information, please see our Terms of Service.

##### Non-personally identifiable information

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you whenever you interact with our website or use the Service, such as your browser name, operating system, Internet Service Provider (ISP) and other related technical information that does not personally identifiable with you.

##### Web browser cookies

Our website may also use “cookies” to learn more about enhance your experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the website may not function properly.

##### How we use collected information

The Receptionist for iPad collects and uses your personal and non-personal information for the following purposes:

  * To personalize the user experience – We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our visitors and customers as a group use the services and resources provided on our website.
  * To improve our website – We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback that you send us.
  * To improve customer service – Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To administer marketing, surveys or other features on our website
  * To send you information that you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you.
  * To send periodic emails – The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. It may also be used to respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. By entering your email address in a form on our website you will be added to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, in the case of visitor logs and other data about our customer’s employees and visitors that are generated and stored in connection with the Service, we will not use any personally identifiable information for any purpose other than providing and improving the Service to that particular customer. We understand that such information is considered confidential by our customers.

##### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our website. Sensitive and private data exchange between the website and you happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. For additional information you may request our Security Overview by emailing [support@thereceptionist.com](mailto:support@thereceptionist.com)

##### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent your personally identifiable information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

##### EU and Swiss Residents

We will use commercially reasonable efforts to comply with the U.S.–E.U. and U.S.– Swiss Safe Harbor principles, located at: <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>. In particular and without limiting the foregoing, we encourage you to contact us at any time should you wish for us to discontinue our use of your personally identifiable information, at which time we will destroy our copies of such information upon your written request. We also encourage you to use the contact information below to inform us of any complaints or disputes you may have regarding the use of your personal information. We will thoroughly investigate the matter internally and make every effort to attempt to resolve the issue quickly. If your dispute cannot be resolved by us internally, we agree to dispute resolution with the Better Business Bureau as our third party resolution provider.

##### Third-party websites

You may find advertising or other content on our website that link to the websites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these websites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website. In addition, these websites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These websites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our website, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

##### Changes to this Privacy Policy

The Receptionist for iPad has the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the top of this page. We encourage you to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

##### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

##### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, our data handling practices or your dealings with this website, please contact us at [support@thereceptionist.com](mailto:support@thereceptionist.com).
